[{"answer": "No.  I don't even know why I do it", "docId": "Rebel_Without_A_Cause.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I'll never get close to anybody", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Can you tell me why you killed the puppies, my friend", "docId": "Rebel_Without_A_Cause.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What do you think's going to happen, you do things like that", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I don't see what's so bad about taking a little drink", "docId": "Rebel_Without_A_Cause.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No.  I definitely don't.  I did the s", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " He called me chicken", "docId": "Rebel_Without_A_Cause.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "They never do", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Mothe", "docId": "Rebel_Without_A_Cause.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "My first day of school, mother'd make me eat and by golly I could never even swallow till reces", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " See", "docId": "Rebel_Without_A_Cause.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " \"Life can be beautiful", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "\"Life is crushing in on me", "docId": "Rebel_Without_A_Cause.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Where what was", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "See, I'm new", "docId": "Rebel_Without_A_Cause.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You're really flippe", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Rebel_Without_A_Cause.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I don't want to make friends", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "But the same song.  I think it's fantastic", "docId": "Rebel_Without_A_Cause.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Are you and Mom home tonight", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What you say your name was", "docId": "Rebel_Without_A_Cause.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Buzz my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "N", "docId": "Rebel_Without_A_Cause.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I think I should go home", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "He's going to cheese, I tell you. Nobody arrested him", "docId": "Rebel_Without_A_Cause.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No.  We're going to bring him down", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I think I should go home", "docId": "Rebel_Without_A_Cause.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Crunc", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "It doesn't matter to them", "docId": "Rebel_Without_A_Cause.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " N", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I don't know, but we can't stay here", "docId": "Rebel_Without_A_Cause.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I'm never going back", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Where's my friend", "docId": "Rebel_Without_A_Cause.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No.  No, I don't", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " Want to read any books?  Take your pick!  Isn't this the craziest", "docId": "Rebel_Without_A_Cause.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Hi", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "We heard firing.  He get anybody? You alone", "docId": "Rebel_Without_A_Cause.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "How'd he get in", "qsentId": 38}]